Preliminary Guide to the Marine Laboratory Records, 1931-2006 UA.18.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0075
  - Oversize Photographs, 5 folders (Box 69)
- Accession UA2018.0085
  - Loose photographs and photocopies (Box 70)
  - Cruises, 1993 (Box 70)
  - Publicity (Box 70)
  - unlabeled folder (Box 70)
  - bound reports and manuals (Box 70)
  - unlabeled folder (Box 70)
  - loose materials (Box 70)
  - Marine operations group photo, 1996 March (Box 70)
  - Oceanography consortium (Box 70)
  - Cape Hatteras crew mughsots for Quentin, 1994 December (Box 70)
  - NAML file, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Faculty bylaws, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Job description, 1997-2000 (Box 70)
  - SCAMPI, 1998 (Box 70)
  - CASE, 1998 (Box 70)
  - External review, 2000 January (Box 70)
  - NSOE website, 2000 February (Box 70)
  - Human Resources job change file, 1997 August (Box 70)
  - Advisory Board misc (Box 70)
  - Hot tuna, 1998 (Box 70)
  - Recruiting, 1998 (Box 70)
  - Belise (Box 70)
  - Misc publications, 1997-1998 (Box 70)
  - Scott Taylor: chronicle ad rates, communication, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Administrative notes Jim Pattray, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Tim Boynton (Box 70)
  - NSOE publications, 1997 (Box 70)
  - unfoldered publications (Box 70)
  - CC27 rating appeal, 1987 October 18 (Box 70)
  - Technical data (Box 70)
  - Technical clips: to be put in book some fateful day (Box 70)
  - 2 1/4 negatives of Rachel Carson book, Fischer plaque, dead girl photo, menhaden plant aerial, 1999 (Box 70)
  - POSES (Box 70)
  - loose materials (Box 70)
  - Hatteras trip photos by Cindy Weeks, 1987 March (Box 70)
  - Halley's Comet: thanks Bruce (Box 70)
  - Barber (Box 70)
  - Maps for 50th anniversary pictures (Box 70)
  - House: Ann St. (Box 70)
  - Cruise pictures by Barber and Francisco (Box 70)
  - Aquanautics (Box 70)
  - Newsletter, 1998 Fall (Box 70)
  - Bft. Exp., 1999 Spring (Box 70)
  - Ambassadors, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Miscelleneous recruiting, 2000 (Box 70)
  - SAML, 1988 December (Box 70)
  - Slideshow script, 1984 March (Box 70)
  - NCIHS Wilmington video info (Box 70)
  - newsletters and publications (Box 70)
  - Eastward photos (Box 70)
  - Progress Report Duke University Cooperative Research and Training Program in Biological Oceanography, 1966-1967 (Box 71)
  - Duke University Cooperative Research and Training Program in Biological Oceanography Data Report for R/V Eastward Cruises, 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 71)
  - Reduced Data Report for R/V Eastward Cruise, 1974; 2 items (Box 71)
  - Scrapbook: Bigelow Laboratory 10th anniversary (Box 72)
- Accession UA2018.0080
  - Publications (Box 72)